chaindd.com 2019-04-17

# PrivacyPolicy

**I. GENERAL  
**

Individuals who visit the http://www.chainsights.chaindd.com website (“Visitors” or “You”) are important to ChainDD, Inc (“we” or “us”). We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of our Visitors and we endeavor to collect only the minimum amount of information needed to meet the purposes for which this website was created. This privacy policy (“Policy”) is designed to inform our Visitors about how their personal information is collected, used, and shared when they visit our website. Visitors should read the Policy carefully and be cautious about providing personally identifiable information without a clear understanding of how the information will be used.

We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy at any time. As the Policy is subject to updates, we encourage you to review this Policy from time to time to better protect your information privacy and security. 

By using our website, you are acknowledging that you understand and agree to the terms of this Policy.

 **II. COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF NON-PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

 **1\. Web Cookies**

Cookies are tiny pieces of data stored by your browser that help a website or service to recognize your unique computer. We use cookies on the website to keep track of services you have used, to keep you logged into the website and to facilitate potential purchase procedures. We also use cookies to track the pages that you visit during each website session, both to help us improve your experiences and to help us understand how the website is being used.

You can remove or block cookies by changing the settings of your browser. Visitors who do not wish to have web cookies placed on their computers and other digital devices should set their browsers to refuse web cookies before accessing the website, with the understanding that certain features of the website may not function properly without the aid of web cookies. Visitors who refuse cookies assume all responsibility for any resulting loss of functionality.

 **2\. Web Beacons And Other Similar Technologies**

Web beacons and other similar technologies, such as tags and pixels, are techniques we may use to compile aggregated statistics about website usage. Specifically, they are electronic files used to record information about how you browse a website. These files are usually invisible to you and allow website operators to check whether you have viewed a particular webpage. We may use beacons or other similar technologies on our website to count our Visitors who have visited particular pages and to deliver co-branded services.

Web beacons collect only a limited set of information, including a web cookies number, time and date of a page view and a description of the page on which the web beacon resides. You may not decline web beacons, but they can be rendered ineffective by declining all web cookies or modifying your browser setting to notify you each time a web cookies is tendered.

 **3\. Analytics**

We may use third-party vendors who use first-party cookies and third-party cookies together to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past activity on our website, including Google Analytics for Display Advertising. The information collected may be used to, among other things, analyze and track date, determine the popularity of certain content and better understand online activity.

If you do not want any information to be collected and used by Google Analytics, you can install an opt-out in your web browser and/or opt out from Google Analytics for Display Advertising or the Google Display Network by using Google’s Ads Setting.

 **4\. Aggregated Information**

We may use your data to produce and share aggregated insights that do not identify you. For example we may use your data to generate statistics about our members, their profession or industry, to calculate ad impressions served or clicked on, or to publish visitor demographics for a demographic workforce insight.

 **5\. Data Acquired from Mobile Device**

If you use a mobile device to access our website, or to download any of our applications, we may collect device information, such as your mobile device ID, model and manufacturer, operating system and IP address.

 **6\. Other**

Our services are dynamic, and we often introduce new features, which may require the collection of new information to our website. If we collect materially different non-personally-identifying data or materially change how we use your data, we will notify you and may also modify this Policy.

 **III. COLLECTION, USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONALLY-IDENTIFYING INFORMATION**

 **1\. Account Registration and Log-in**

To create an account on our website and to log in your account on our website, you need to provide data including your mobile number and a password. W

 **2\. Profile**

You have choices about the information on your profile, such as your education, work experience, skills, photo, city or area and endorsements. It’s your choice whether to include sensitive information on your profile and to make that sensitive information public. Please do not post or add personal data to your profile that you would not want to be publicly available.

 **3\. Online Posting and Uploading**

We may provide areas on the website where you can post reviews, comments, and other information relating to your activities on the website. In that case, we collect personal data from you when you provide, post or upload it to our website, such as when you fill out a form, (e.g., with demographic data or salary), respond to a survey, participate in polls, contests, or other features of our service, respond to offers or advertisements, or register for an event we host. In addition, such postings may appear on other websites or when searches are executed on the subject of your posting.

Please be advised that whenever you voluntarily disclose personally-identifying information on publicly-viewable web pages, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. We cannot control who reads your posting, or what other users may do with the information you voluntarily post, so we encourage you to exercise discretion and caution with respect to your personal information. Visitors assume all responsibility for any loss of privacy or other harm resulting from their voluntary disclosure of personally-identifying information.

 **4\. Customer Support**

We use your personally-identifying data, which can include your communications, to investigate, respond to and resolve complaints and service issues.

 **5\. Company Communication**

We may occasionally contact you regarding new services offered by us through email, mobile phone, notices posted on our websites or apps, and other ways through our services, including text messages and push notifications. We may send you messages about the availability of our services, security, or other service-related issues. We may also send messages about how to use the services, network updates, reminders, and promotional messages from us and our partners. Generally, you may opt out of such communications at the time of registration or through your account settings, though we reserve the right to send you notices about your account, including security and legal notices.

 **6\. Social Media**

We may use hyperlinks on our website which will redirect you to a social network if you click on the respective link. However, when you click on a social plug-in, such as Facebook’s “Like” button, that particular social network’s plugin will be activated and your browser will directly connected to that provider’s servers. 

If you do not wish to use these buttons, none of your data will be sent to the respective social network’s plugin provider. Settings regarding privacy protection can be found on the website to these social networks and are not within our control.

 **7\. Company Legal Disclosures**

It is possible that we will need to disclose personally-identifying information about you when required by law, subpoena, or other legal process or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to

(a) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, fraud or other wrongdoing;

(b) assist government enforcement agencies; 

(c) comply with applicable law;

(d) enforce our agreements and policies with you;

(e) investigate, protect and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations;

(f) protect the security or integrity of our service (such as by sharing with companies facing similar threats); or 

(g) exercise or protect the rights, property and safety of our company, our personnel, or others. 

In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us.

 **8\. Service Providers**

We use third-party providers to help us provide our services, such as maintenance, analysis, audit, payments, fraud detection, marketing and development. They will have access to your information as reasonably necessary to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for other purposes.

 **9\. Change in Control or Sale**

We reserve the right to transfer all personally-identifying information in our possession to a successor organization in the event of a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy or other sale of all or a portion of our assets. Any other successor organization which buys us or part of our business will have the right to continue to use your data, but only in the manner set out in this Policy unless you agree otherwise.

 **IV. SECURITY**

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via our website, we use reasonable electronic, personnel and physical measures to protect it from loss, theft, alteration or misuse. we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers and servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

However, please be advised that even the best security measures cannot fully eliminate all risks. We cannot guarantee that only authorized persons will view your information. We are not responsible for third-party circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures.

It is your responsibility to maintain the confidentiality of your personally-identifying information by keeping your password confidential. You should change your password immediately if you believe someone has gained unauthorized access to it or your account. If you lose control of your account, your should notify us immediate.

 **V. CHILDREN**

The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) protects the online privacy of children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly collect or maintain personally-identifying information from anyone under the age of 13, unless or except as permitted by law. Any person who provides personally-identifying information through the website represents to us that he or she is 13 years of age or older. If we learn that personally-identifying information has been collected from a Visitor under 13 years of age on or through our website, then we will take the appropriate steps to cause this information to be deleted. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has become a member of our website or has otherwise transferred personally-identifying information to our website, please contact us using our contact information below to have that child’s account terminated and information deleted.

 **VI. DO-NOT-TRACK POLICY**

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. Our website does currently respond to DNT browser signals or mechanisms.

 **VII. CONTACT**

If you have questions or complaints regarding this Policy, please first contact (646) 988-8916, or event@chaindd.com. You can also reach us by physical mail at

12 E 49th Street, 17 Fl, New York, NY 10017
